Sarah this has never happened and if I
move it sink
slower
oh Sarah help me and my kayak
sing
Sarah Sarah I don't know what to do I
can't help it I'm sorry can you get my
stand up no yes no there's it's too
deep it's on your
[Music]
shirt Sarah me oh my god oh
no Sarah leave him go on with your life
Sarah nobody expects a red head to
survive
outside that capsized tomato face as Max
and he almost drowned in class zero
Rapids kayak is spelled the same
backwards as forwards which is the only
interesting thing about it kayaks just
aren't my kind of boat because you can't
fit five naked on the back about
but mostly because I have no desire to
own a Toyota FJ
Cruiser kaying is something old people
pretend to do before or aftering in
Viagra commercials I assume after but
that campaign is confusing girls say
they like an outdoorsy man but that's
just because they haven't seen the
inside of my house the only time I'm
wasting a weekend hiking is when my team
has a buy and by hiking I mean walking
up a hill so you can take a selfie and
walk back down if you crave sunshine and
an active lifestyle so much enlist
nothing like taking heavy fire in a
desert for 2 years but if Max wants to
explore the Great Outdoors I'll slather
that Ginger and SPF a jillion and fly to
Hollywood where people connect with
nature by going outside to talk on their
cell phones in this week's web
[Music]
[Applause]
Redemption Daniel is a 28-year-old host
of a television show on Comedy Central
for his one item he asked to bring a gun
producers said no he then asked for a
million dollars which was also rejected
so he asked for 50 wishes we explained
that the show is not a genie after
denying him a cute 2 bed 2 and 1 half
bath cabin he asked what would be in his
mystery basket and we told him that this
isn't chopped so he got angry and said
fine I'm not bringing anything then 5
minutes later he called back and asked
about a 24t long hogy from Subway he
said no so he settled on bringing butt
wipes Max is a 20-some ginger with a
fear of
water hey Daniel hey he must be
yeah
how sry anytime I'm naked and afraid I
get the worst fear boners what item did
you bring I brought a cure egg genius I
know I was hoping you'd have some K Cups
I should have I just brought butt wipes
smart can I use one don't test me how
old are you I am 21 21 years old and
where was that video it was in northern
Wisconsin was it a lake it was a river
what are your your survival skills like
oh God terrible I'm uncoordinated I'm
not athletic and I hate nature we're
going to die out here oh
no
no why did you freak out because it was
about 5T of water but then 6 ft of muck
it was gross I was like I didn't want to
touch the bottom no one wants to touch
that stuff who wants to deal with fish
they're like under fish you have to eat
them not even you don't have to eat fish
no they don't have legs and of course
they don't have right well it's like
snakes I don't like it I don't want to
eat snakes though right no Seafood what
about shrimp I can do like cocktail
shrimp they have and and and lobster
they have legs I don't like lobster they
have legs yeah I don't like lobster
anyway what does a scallop look like
when it's alive um I have no idea
Sarah Sarah I don't know what to do were
you upset with your friend
Sarah uh no there wasn't much she could
do I assume she didn't start filming
immediately so how long she did I was
ahead of her she came up behind me heard
me screaming and just pulled out the
camera how long are you out of the kayak
for like an hour so for an hour Sarah
did nothing she sort of just floated
around me did you go to the bathroom in
the in the water yeah no the whole you
out there for over an hour yeah I always
go when I'm in the water you ever shop
at
reii like an outdoorsy store no I don't
smart wool socks they sell those I'm a
fan of a good sock I I like socks I have
a lot of crazy socks yeah fun socks are
the kind of the thing right now they are
yeah don't worry about that okay enough
of the small talk first things first if
we're going to survive for 21 days we
need to determine what day of the week
is date night why do we need a date
night it's good for morale I'm going to
spend the whole day preparing a fancy
make believe meal and then we're going
to make love all right but first we need
some clothes
[Music]
yes great you found some fruit is there
any more no it's all for my hat now
let's go build some
shelter it's night one I'm hungry I'm
thirsty and Daniel spent most of the day
sunbathing who are you talking
to I can't sleep I think I left my
garage door open where did you get a
mask found it in a
tree
sarah
sarah sarah
Sarah
in just 21 days Daniel populated
gentrified and industrialized an entire
civilization from
scratch he invented a highly complex
language and led the colony to victories
in two separate Wars which has formed a
utopian society with a zero crime rate
Max spent the majority of his time
crying look what we've accomplished we
made it we finally get to go home today
we just have to get across shark
lake named after John shark I'm
hoping what's happening aren't you ready
to go
home Daniel is
[Music]
home
I'm sinking Daniel help me please I
don't know what to do I'm
sinking as his Colony continues to
flourish Daniel finishes with the
greatest primitive survival rating in
the show's history Max however died of a
mild panic attack in under 2 ft of water
the show was cancelled as the camera
crew showed gross negligence in allowing
a contestant to slowly die in front of
them many of my people are here tonight
cute
[Music]
C